University of Connecticut 1987.0011
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series II: Administration, 1974-1985; 1979-1985
  - Exchange Program
    - Belgrade, Yugoslavia, 1976-1982 (Box 10:, Folder 263-264)
    - China, 1978-1980 (Box 10:, Folder 265)
    - Egypt-Zagazig, 1979-1983 (Box 10:, Folder 266-267)
    - Faculty-exchange, 1979-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 268)
    - Germany, 1980-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 269)
    - Hungary, 1983 December 13 (Box 10:, Folder 270)
    - Italy, 1980-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 271)
    - Poland, 1981-1982 (Box 10:, Folder 272-273)
    - Paraiba, Brazil, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 274)
    - Portugal, 1979-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 275)
  - Executive Records Divisions, 1979-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 276)
  - Experimental College, 1977 (Box 10:, Folder 277)
  - Extended and continuing education, 1979-1982 (Box 10:, Folder 278-279)
  - F, 1983-1984 (Box 10:, Folder 280)
  - Faculty
    - Part-time, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 281)
    - and administration, 1984 (Box 10:, Folder 282)
    - and administration relations, 1977 March 28 (Box 10:, Folder 283)
    - Alumni Center, 1979-1982 (Box 10:, Folder 284-285)
    - Breakfast, 1982 (Box 10:, Folder 286)
    - Department tuition letters, 1982-1983 (Box 10:, Folder 287)
    - Departments' tuition: tally and certification letters, 1980-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 288)
    - Evaluation by students, 1980-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 289)
    - For Rational Alternatives, 1974, 1977 (Box 10:, Folder 290)
    - Review Board, 1979-1980 (Box 10:, Folder 291)
  - Federation of Students and Service Organizations, 1978-1980 (Box 10:, Folder 292-293)
    [See also: Undergraduate Student Government]
  - Finance and Administration, 1978-1983 (Box 10:, Folder 294-297)
    - Endowment fund/social responsibility, 1979 January - April (Box 10:, Folder 298)
    - Endowment fund/social responsibility, 1979-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 299)
    - Financial aid, 1979-1983 (Box 10:, Folder 300-301)
    - Hartford Seminary, 1977-1983 (Box 10:, Folder 302-304)
    - Property considerations, 1979-1981 (Box 10:, Folder 305)
    - Vice-president search, 1983-1984 (Box 10:, Folder 306-307)
  - Financial aid, 1982-1983 (Box 10:, Folder 308)
  - Financial aid: Selective Service Registration, 1982-1983 (Box 10:, Folder 309)
  - Food service [See: Student Affairs and Services]
  - Founder's Day, 1980 April (Box 10:, Folder 310)
  - Fraternities: campus housing issue, 1974-1980, 1982 (Box 10:, Folder 311-312)
  - Freedom of Information, 1978-1980 (Box 11:, Folder 313)
  - G, 1982 April 16 (Box 11:, Folder 314)
  - Gant, Acting President, 1979 (Box 11:, Folder 315)
  - Gay rights, 1978-1981 (Box 11:, Folder 316)
  - General Studies, Bachelor of, 1980 October (Box 11:, Folder 317)
  - Geography, 1979-1982 (Box 11:, Folder 318)
  - Graduate Education and Research: Vice-president search; Allen, Harold L., Azariff, Leonid V., 1977-1982 (Box 11:, Folder 319-322)
  - Graduate School, 1978-1984 (Box 11:, Folder 323-328)
    - Grad assistant stipend, 1979-1980 (Box 11:, Folder 329)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 11:, Folder 330)
    - Student Council, 1979-1981 (Box 11:, Folder 331-332)
    - Student Organizations, 1981-1982 (Box 11:, Folder 333)
  - Grants and contracts, 1981-1984 (Box 11:, Folder 334)
  - H, 1984 (Box 11:, Folder 335)
  - Harassment [See: Sexual harassment and/or Racism]
  - Hartford Branch, 1979-1981 (Box 11:, Folder 336)
  - Hartford Branch, S.E. branch, 1982-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 337)
  - Hazardous waste treatment laboratory, 1981-1983 (Box 11:, Folder 338-339)
  - Health Center, 1979-1984 (Box 11:, Folder 340-346)
    - Legislative task force, 1984 (Box 11:, Folder 347)
    - Operational flexibility, 1980-1982 (Box 12:, Folder 348-349)
    - Organizations, 1972-1973 (Box 12:, Folder 350)
    - Vice-president search, 1980 (Box 12:, Folder 351)
  - Health professional schools: potential move to Farmington, 1983 July - October (Box 12:, Folder 352)
  - Health services, 1979-1984 (Box 12:, Folder 353-356)
  - Higher, technical and adult education, 1979-1983 (Box 12:, Folder 357-358)
  - High Technology Council, 1983 (Box 12:, Folder 359)
  - Hilltop Council, 1976 December 16 (Box 12:, Folder 360)
  - Home Economics [See also: School of Family Studies], 1974-1981 (Box 12:, Folder 361-362)
  - Homer Babbidge Library: hours reduction, 1980 (Box 12:, Folder 363)
  - Homer Babbidge Library, 1978-1981 (Box 12:, Folder 364-365)
  - Honorary degrees, 1978-1981 (Box 12:, Folder 366)
  - Honors program, 1977 July - September (Box 12:, Folder 367)
  - Horticulture Club, 1980 October (Box 12:, Folder 368)
  - Housing: rental fee increases, 1980-1982 (Box 12:, Folder 369)
  - I, 1982 (Box 12:, Folder 370)
  - Image, 1982 (Box 12:, Folder 371)
  - Institute and Department of Marine Science, 1979-1980, 1983 (Box 12:, Folder 372-373)
  - Institute of Materials Science: Advisory Board, 1979-1983 (Box 12:, Folder 374-376)
  - Institute of Public Service, 1979-1982 (Box 12:, Folder 377-378)
  - Institute for Social Inquiry, 1980-1983 (Box 12:, Folder 379-380)
  - Institute of Urban Research, 1974-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 381)
  - Institute of Water Resources, 1979-1982 (Box 12:, Folder 382-383)
  - Institutional memberships, 1979 April (Box 12:, Folder 384)
  - Institutional research [See: Office of Institutional Research]
  - International Conference, October 1980, 1970 September 27 (Box 12:, Folder 385)
  - International programs, 1979-1983 (Box 12:, Folder 386-389)
  - Inventory, 1983 (Box 12:, Folder 390)
  - Jewish Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 12:, Folder 391)
  - Job Classification Committee, 1981 July - August (Box 12:, Folder 392)
  - Jorgensen, Albert N., 1978-1983 (Box 12:, Folder 393-394)
  - Jorgensen Auditorium, 1977-1982 (Box 12:, Folder 395-396)
  - Judaic Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 397)
  - Kappa Kappa fraternity, 1982 April 27 (Box 12:, Folder 398)
  - L, 1983-1984 (Box 12:, Folder 399)
  - Labor Education Center, 1979-1981 (Box 12:, Folder 400)
  - Latin American studies, 1982-83 (Box 12:, Folder 401)
  - Law School, 1977-1981 (Box 12:, Folder 402-403)
  - Law School, 1982-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 404)
    - Accreditation, 1982-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 405)
    - Admissions, 1979-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 406-407)
    - Foundation audits, 1975-1986 (Box 13:, Folder 408)
    - School renovations, 1983-1984 (Box 13:, Folder 409)
  - M, 1981-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 410)
  - Mansfield (town), 1976-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 411)
  - Mail service, University, 1978-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 412)
  - Masters of Public Affairs program, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 413)
  - McMahon, Brien Lecture, 1979-1980 (Box 13:, Folder 414)
  - Merit increases, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 415)
  - Microcosm on racial relations [See also: Minorities], 1982-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 416)
  - Mid-East Language & Area Studies Center, 1979-1980 (Box 13:, Folder 417)
  - Middle East Studies Group, 1980 (Box 13:, Folder 418)
  - Minorities Center for Academic Programs, 1980-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 419)
  - Minority Graduate Student Associations, 1981 August 21 (Box 13:, Folder 420)
  - Minority/Majority relations: Tucket/Alderfer Report, 1980-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 421)
  - Minorities: microcosm, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 422)
  - Minorities, 1979-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 423-424)
  - Mission statement, 1976 (Box 13:, Folder 425)
  - Moving expenses, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 426)
  - Museum of Natural History, 1982-1985 (Box 13:, Folder 427)
  - N, 1982-1984 (Box 13:, Folder 428)
  - N.C.A.A. [See: Athletics—NCAA]
  - National Society of Black Engineers, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 429)
  - Nepotism allegations: Hartford campus, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 430)
  - New England Research Application Center (NERAC), 1979-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 431-432)
  - Nutmeg, 1975, 1981-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 433-434)
  - O, 1982-1984 (Box 13:, Folder 435)
  - Objectives, short-term, 1980 (Box 13:, Folder 436)
  - Office for Affirmative Action Programs, 1979-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 437-442)
    - Affirmative action progress, 1983-1984 (Box 14:, Folder 443)
  - Office of Facilities, 1982-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 444-445)
  - Office of Institutional Research, 1979-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 446-452)
    - Program files, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 453)
    - Supplemental Information, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 454)
  - Office of Internal Auditing, 1978-1984 (Box 14:, Folder 455-456)
  - Office of Public Information, 1979-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 457-458)
  - Office of Rental Properties and Telecommunications, 1981-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 459-460)
  - Ombudsman, 1979-1984 (Box 14:, Folder 461-463)
  - Ombudsman: Student, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 464)
  - Organization charts, 1980-1981 (Box 14:, Folder 465)
  - P, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 466)
  - Parents and friends letters, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 467)
  - Parking, 1979-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 468-469)
  - Pathobiology building, 1979-1980 (Box 14:, Folder 470)
  - Payroll, 1979, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 471-472)
  - Personnel, 1979-1984 (Box 14:, Folder 473-474)
  - Personnel policies: reclass/upgrade/fund, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 475)
  - Phi Alpha Theta, 1981 June (Box 14:, Folder 476)
  - Photolab, 1979, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 477-478)
  - Physical plant [See also: Office of Facilities], 1979-1980 (Box 14:, Folder 479)
  - Physical plant, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 480)
  - Placement, 1979, 1981 (Box 14:, Folder 481)
  - Policy research, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 482)
  - Policy statements, 1979-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 483-484)
  - Pornography, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 485)
  - President, 1978-1984 (Box 14:, Folder 486-488)
  - Presidential Advisory Search Committee, 1980 November 11 (Box 14:, Folder 489)
  - President's Contingency Fund [See: Alumni Association—President's Contingency Fund, UConn Foundation—President's Contingency Fund]
  - President
    - Driver, 1981-1983 (Box 14:, Folder 490)
    - Internal fiscal management, 1980-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 491)
    - Internal Fiscal Management Committee, 1983 (Box 15:, Folder 492)
    - Newsletter, 1983 (Box 15:, Folder 493)
    - Report to the Senate, 1980-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 494)
    - Office
      - Internships, 1977-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 495-497)
      - Renovations, 1980 (Box 15:, Folder 498)
      - Staff, 1976-1981, 1983 (Box 15:, Folder 499-500)
  - Public Affairs, 1983 (Box 15:, Folder 501)
  - Public Safety Division, 1978-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 502-503)
  - Puerto Rican concern, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 504)
  - Purchasing department, 1981-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 505)
  - R, 1984 (Box 15:, Folder 506)
  - Racism, 1979-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 507-508)
  - Radio and television center, 1979 (Box 15:, Folder 509)
  - Reappointment, 1979 (Box 15:, Folder 510)
  - Recruitment, 1981 Feb (Box 15:, Folder 511)
  - Registrar, 1979-1982 (Box 15:, Folder 512-513)
  - Research Council, 1975-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 514)
  - Research and Development Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 15:, Folder 515-516)
    [See also: Development]
  - Research Foundation, 1979-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 517-518)
  - Research Park, 1981-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 519-520)
  - Residence Halls, 1977-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 521-523)
  - Residential Life [See also: Student Affairs and Services], 1982-1984 (Box 15:, Folder 524-526)
  - Resource directory; government officials, undated (Box 15:, Folder 527)
  - Retirement coffees, 1979 (Box 15:, Folder 528)
  - Ribicoff Research Center, 1980 April 14 (Box 15:, Folder 529)
  - Ridesharing, 1979-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 530)
  - Roper Center, 1979-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 531-534)
  - R.O.T.C., 1979-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 535-537)
  - S, 1983-1984 (Box 15:, Folder 538)
  - Sabbatic leave, 1978-1979 (Box 15:, Folder 539)
  - Safety, campus, 1977-1984 (Box 15:, Folder 540-543)
  - Salaries, 1979-1983 (Box 15:, Folder 544-546)
  - Scholarships (Box not specified)
    - Jr. Miss, 1980 (Box 16:, Folder 547)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 548)
    - Root Tilden, 1975-1981 (Box 16:, Folder 549)
    - Harry S. Truman, 1976-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 550-551)
  - School of Business Administration, 1979-1984 (Box 16:, Folder 552-557)
  - School of Dental Medicine: Admissions inquiries, 1980-1981 (Box 16:, Folder 558)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 1979-1982 (Box 16:, Folder 559)
  - School of Education, 1979-1984 (Box 16:, Folder 560-562)
  - School of Engineering, 1979-1984 (Box 16:, Folder 563-567)
    - Accreditation, 1978-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 568-569)
    - Electrical Engineering: Computer Science split, 1978-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 570)
  - School of Fine Arts, 1978-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 571)
  - School of Medicine, 1979-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 572-575)
  - School of Nursing, 1979-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 576-577)
  - School of Pharmacy, 1979-1982 (Box 16:, Folder 578-580)
  - School of Social Work, 1979-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 581-584)
  - Scuba Club, 1980 January (Box 16:, Folder 585)
  - Sea Grant Program, 1980-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 586-587)
  - Search procedures, 1978-1982 (Box 16:, Folder 588-589)
  - Section 504 Transition Plan, 1985 (Box 16:, Folder 590)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1980-1983 (Box 16:, Folder 591-592)
  - Sidewalk construction Rt. 195, proposed, 1976, 1979-1980 (Box 17:, Folder 593)
  - Sigma Chi, 1981 Oct 8 (Box 17:, Folder 594)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1976-1979 (Box 17:, Folder 595)
  - Small Business Administration, 1980-1981 (Box 17:, Folder 596)
  - Social Science Data Center, 1979 (Box 17:, Folder 597)
    [See also: Institute for Social Inquiry]
  - Southeastern Branch, 1979-1984 (Box 17:, Folder 598-602)
    - Branford House, 1979-1983 (Box 17:, Folder 603-608)
    - Coast Guard, 1979-1982 (Box 17:, Folder 609-610)
    - Noank House, 1984 March (Box 17:, Folder 611)
    - Noank, N.E. Research Lab, 1982-1983 (Box 17:, Folder 612)
  - Space allocation, 1977-1981
    - Gulley Hall, 1978-1983 (Box 17:, Folder 613-614)
    - Hartford, 1978-1982 (Box 17:, Folder 615-616)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 17:, Folder 617)
    - Wilbur Cross Library, 1975-1982 (Box 17:, Folder 618-619)
  - Special Olympics proposal, 1982-1984 (Box 17:, Folder 620)
  - Special Student Services, 1979 (Box 17:, Folder 621)
  - Stamford Branch, 1979-1985 (Box 17:, Folder 622-625)
  - Stamford Campus Council, 1980-1981 (Box 17:, Folder 626)
  - State Archaeologist, 1983 September (Box 17:, Folder 627)
  - Student Affairs and Services, 1979-1984 (Box 17:, Folder 628-631)
    - Buczynski, Ruth M., 1980 (Box 17:, Folder 632)
    - Commons dining halls, 1979 (Box 17:, Folder 633)
    - Day of Pride, 1976-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 634)
    - Disciplinary actions, 1981-1984 (Box 18:, Folder 635)
    - Food services, 1979-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 636)
    - Orientation, 1979-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 637)
    - Residential Life, 1980-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 638-639)
    - Review of departments, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 640)
    - University Report Relating to Changes, 1981 January 27 (Box 18:, Folder 641)
    - Vice-President search, 1980-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 642)
  - Student Federal Credit Union, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 643)
  - Student Labor, 1982-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 644-645)
  - Student organizations, 1982-1986 (Box 18:, Folder 646-647)
  - Student Union, 1977-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 648)
  - Student Union Board of Governors, 1979-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 649-650)
  - Subcommittee on T.V. Spots (S.E.C.), 1980 (Box 18:, Folder 651)
  - Summer session, 1979-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 652)
  - T.A.F.S. (Trustee-Administration-Faculty-Student) Committee, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 653)
  - Taylor, Hal—research consultant, 1977-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 654)
  - Teaching Resource Council, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 655)
  - Technical Services Center, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 656)
  - Telecommunications., 1983 December 19 (Box 18:, Folder 657)
  - Telephone expense summaries, 1985 (Box 18:, Folder 658)
  - Telephone service, 1979-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 659-660)
  - Tenure, 1979-1980 (Box 18:, Folder 661)
  - Torrington Branch, 1979-1985 (Box 18:, Folder 662-666)
  - Transportation Department, 1979-1980 (Box 18:, Folder 667)
  - Transportation Institute, 1979-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 668)
  - Travel information, 1979-1980 (Box 18:, Folder 669)
  - Tucker/Alderfer Report [See: Minority/Majority Relations] (Box 18:, Folder 670)
  - Tuition and fees, 1979-1984 (Box 18:, Folder 671-674)
  - Uncas-on-Thames, 1984 (Box 18:, Folder 675)
  - Undergraduate Student Government, 1980-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 676-677)
  - United Nations Day, 1980-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 678)
  - University Archives, 1980 (Box 19, Folder data_value_missing_6155c4795ed5d9c5a27ce31df7e0c370)
  - University of Connecticut Educational Properties, Inc. (U.C.E.P.I.), 1982-1984 (Box 19:, Folder 679-690)
  - University of Connecticut Foundation, 1979-1984 (Box 19:, Folder 691-694)
    - Parents and friends letters, 1980 (Box 19:, Folder 695)
    - President's Contingency Fund, 1981-1984 (Box 19:, Folder 696-699)
  - University of Connecticut League, 1977 September 20 (Box 20:, Folder 700)
  - University of Connecticut Professional Employees Association (U.C.P.E.A.) [See: Collective Bargaining]
  - University of Riyadh, 1980 (Box 20:, Folder 701)
  - University Press of New England, 1984 (Box 20:, Folder 702)
  - University Professor, 1964, 1979-1984 (Box 20:, Folder 703-704)
  - University publications, 1979-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 705-706)
  - University Relations, 1980 Sep (Box 20:, Folder 707-708)
  - University seal/name: use of, 1980 April 29 (Box 20:, Folder 709)
  - Urban studies, 1980 (Box 20:, Folder 710)
  - U.S.D.A. violations: animal care, 1984 (Box 20:, Folder 711-712)
  - Veterinary medicine, 1981-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 713-714)
  - Wang supplies, 1981 Oct 22 (Box 20:, Folder 715)
  - Waterbury branch, 1979-1984 (Box 20:, Folder 716-719)
  - Waugh, Albert, 1980 May (Box 20:, Folder 720)
  - W.H.U.S., 1979-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 721-722)
  - William Benton Museum of Art, 1979-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 723-724)
  - Women's Center, 1979-1982 (Box 20:, Folder 725-726)
  - Women's Studies Program, 1978-1979 (Box 20:, Folder 727)
- Series III: State Government, undated, 1952-1986
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Structure of Higher Education, 1978-1981 (Box 20A:, Folder 728)
  - Administrative services, 1982-1983 (Box 21:, Folder 729)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 21:, Folder 730)
  - Asnuntuck Community College, 1978-1980 (Box 21:, Folder 731)
  - Attorney General, 1971-1983 (Box 21:, Folder 732-733)
  - Auditors, 1980-1984 (Box 21:, Folder 734-741)
  - B, 1979 (Box 21:, Folder 742)
  - Bill #5655: Tuition waver, 1976 January - March (Box 21:, Folder 743)
  - Board of Governors, 1976, 1982-1983 (Box 21:, Folder 744-745)
  - Board of Higher Education, 1979-1980 March (Box 21:, Folder 746-752)
  - Board of Higher Education, 1980-1982 April (Box 22:, Folder 753-765)
  - Board of Regents
    - Legislative contact by constituent, 1976 June (Box 22:, Folder 766)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976 April - May (Box 22:, Folder 767)
    - Press (Box 22:, Folder 768)
    - Prior to April 1976 (restructuring), 1975-1976 (Box 22:, Folder 769)
    - Resolutions of Opposition, 1976 March (Box 22:, Folder 770)
  - Board for State Academic Awards, 1979-1981 (Box 22:, Folder 771)
  - Board for State Academy, 1982 (Box 22:, Folder 772)
  - Board of Trustees of Regional Community Colleges, 1979-1983 (Box 22:, Folder 773-774)
  - Board of Trustees" State colleges, 1981-1982 (Box 22:, Folder 775-776)
  - Board of Trustees for State Technical Colleges, 1979-1981 (Box 22:, Folder 777)
  - Buckley Amendment, 1978-1980 (Box 22:, Folder 778)
  - Budget, undated (Box 23:, Folder 779-780)
  - Bureau of Purchases, 1978-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 781)
  - C, 1979-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 782)
  - Central Connecticut State College, 1980 (Box 23:, Folder 783)
  - Chief Executive Officers, 1984 (Box 23:, Folder 784)
  - Coordinating Council, 1979-1981 (Box 23:, Folder 785)
  - Commission on the Arts, 1981 (Box 23:, Folder 786)
  - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities, 1982-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 787)
  - Comptroller, 1982-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 788-789)
  - Connecticut Alcohol and Drug Abuse Commission, 1978-1981 (Box 23:, Folder 790)
  - Connecticut Council for Higher Education, 1975-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 791-796)
  - Connecticut Joint Council on Economic Education, 1982 (Box 23:, Folder 797)
  - D, 1982-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 798)
  - Degrees offered in Connecticut, 1979 (Box 23:, Folder 799)
  - Department of Administrative Services, 1978-1981 (Box 23:, Folder 800)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1980 (Box 23:, Folder 801)
  - Department of Economic Development, 1976-1980, 1983 March - February (Box 23:, Folder 802-803)
  - Department of Education, 1981, 1983 (Box 23:, Folder 804-805)
  - Department of Environmental Protection, 1975-1982 (Box 23:, Folder 806-807)
  - Department of Health, 1975-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 808-809)
  - Department of Higher Education, 1983 January - 1984 February (Box 23:, Folder 810-818)
  - Department of Higher Education, 1984 February - December (Box 24:, Folder 819-825)
    - Affirmative Action Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 24:, Folder 826)
    - Enrollment reports, 1978-1983 (Box 24:, Folder 827-828)
    - Extension funds, 1979-1981 (Box 24:, Folder 829)
    - Faculty advisor, 1977-1981 (Box 24:, Folder 830)
    - Financial assistance, 1978-1979 (Box 24:, Folder 831)
    - Formula Budgeting Advisory Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 24:, Folder 832)
    - Full-time equivalent, 1978-1980 (Box 24:, Folder 833)
    - Management Information System, 1979, 1982-1983 (Box 24:, Folder 834-835)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 24:, Folder 836)
    - Mission statements, 1984-1986 (Box 24:, Folder 837)
    - Restructuring I, 1978-1979 (Box 24:, Folder 838-839)
    - Restructuring II, 1979 (Box 24:, Folder 840)
    - Restructuring III, 1979-1980 (Box 25:, Folder 841-842)
    - Tuition waver regulation, 1982-1983 (Box 25:, Folder 843)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1975-1978 (Box 25:, Folder 844)
  - Department of Planning and Energy, 1975-1976 (Box 25:, Folder 845)
  - Department of Social Services, 1975 (Box 25:, Folder 846)
  - Department of Transportation, 1976-1879, 1982 (Box 25:, Folder 847-848)
  - Disposition of bills, 1975 General Assembly, 1974-1975 (Box 25:, Folder 849)
  - E, 1984-1985 (Box 25:, Folder 850)
  - Education Planning Committee, 1979 (Box 25:, Folder 851)
  - Federation of Technical College Teachers, 1979 (Box 25:, Folder 852)
  - Finance Subcommittee on Bonding, 1978-1979 (Box 25:, Folder 853-854)
  - Fleet operations, 1979-1982 (Box 25:, Folder 856-857)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1978-1979 (Box 25:, Folder 858)
  - Freedom of Information Commission, 1983 (Box 25:, Folder 859)
  - G - Z, State of Connecticut, 1975-1984 (Box 25:, Folder 860)
  - General Assembly, 1979-1980, 1984 (Box 25:, Folder 861)
  - Government Administration and Policy Committee, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 862)
  - Governor, 1983 August - December (Box 25:, Folder 863)
  - Governor: 4-year Progress Report, 1974, 1974 November - December (Box 25:, Folder 864)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission: School of Veterinary Medicine and Surgery, 1976-1977 (Box 25:, Folder 865)
  - Governor's Council of Economic Advisors, 1976 February - June (Box 25:, Folder 866)
  - Governor's High Technology Council, 1982-1983 (Box 25:, Folder 867)
  - Governor's High Technology Council, 1983 (Box 26:, Folder 868)
  - Governor's Office, 1974-1984 (Box 26:, Folder 869)
  - Greater Hartford Community College, 1981 (Box 26:, Folder 870)
  - H, 1984 (Box 26:, Folder 871)
  - Joint Committee on Education, 1979-1981 (Box 26:, Folder 872)
  - Justice Agency, 1974 (Box 26:, Folder 873)
  - L, 1982-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 874)
  - Labor Department, 1976-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 875-876)
  - Legislative Audit Review Subcommittee, 1981 (Box 26:, Folder 877)
  - Legislative Day, February 7, 1976, 1976 January - March (Box 26:, Folder 878)
  - Legislative Internship Program, 1982 July - November (Box 26:, Folder 879)
  - Legislative inquiries
    - A, 1976-1983 (Box 26:, Folder 880-881)